Class of 1996 Records, 1992-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1996 Records
1992-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1996.
RG 80 UUID:a67958ea-7ae7-4f03-a45e-6af6fb250785
2 boxes (1.9 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1996.
The Class of 1996 was the 118th graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1996 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1996, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1996 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General 1995-1996 (Box 2308, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 2)
- Commencement Speaker 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 3)
- Groups 1993 (Box 2308, Folder 4)
- Junior Ushers 1995 (Box 2308, Folder 5)
- Last Chapel 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 6)
- Newsletters 1996-2002 (Box 2308, Folder 7)
- Reunion 2005-2006 (Box 2308, Folder 8)
- Senior Ball 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 9)
- Senior Class Gift 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 10)
- Senior Newsletter 1995-1996 (Box 2308, Folder 11)
- Speeches and Remarks by Alison J. Wong, Senior Class President 1995-1996 (Box 2308, Folder 12)
- Sophomore Push 1994 (Box 2308, Folder 13)
- Who's Who 1992-1993 (Box 2308, Folder 14)